DAN MFALA







T +90 539 108 0882 E mfaladan@gmail.com A Nicosia, Lefkosa S https://github.com/Danico-mfala

SUMMARY

Graduate in mechatronics with a passion for robotics and software development. I have experience building websites and mobile apps, as well as implementing REST APIs and developing user interfaces. My goal is to combine my engineering and programming skills to create innovative and efficient solutions

EXPERIENCE

May 2022 - Nov 2023 Fullstack developer / CyprusCodes Implementing a REST API using the Xest framework User interface development with React, JavaScript, and CSS.

Jun 2021 - Feb 2022

Summer internship at the mechanical workshop, Cyprus International University

Gained hands-on experience with CNC machines, turning, grinding and laser cutting machines. Practical skills developed in the operation and maintenance of machinery.

Jun 2019 - present

Software developer / Root Tech Control

Part-time, I work as a software developer at Root Tech, where I create websites and mobile apps.

LEADERSHIP

As the web application platform, manager and instructor in the SCAP program at Cyprus International University, I lead the team in charge of creating and maintaining the website. My responsibilities include:

- Introduction and integration of new students to the project.
- Assignment and supervision of tasks.
- Training students in front-end and back-end web development.
- Teaching the use of Arduino software and the creation of robots with different technologies.

EDUCATION

Mechatronics Engineering

Cyprus International University February 2019 - June 2023 Nicosia, Lefkosa

Mechatronic engineering integrates mechanical, electrical and electronic systems. combining robotics, computing, systems, control and product engineering.

Software Engineering

Bootcamp CyprusCodes May 2022 - Nov 2022

7-month software development bootcamp to learn JavaScript, Nodejs, React, MySQL and more

Languages

- **FRENCH**
- **ENGLISH**

SKILLS

- REACT, REACT NATIVE
- PHP, NODE, XEST, NEXT
- GIT, REST API, PYTHON
- HTML5, CSS, C++, SQL
- SOLIDWORK, RDWORKS